[{"id": 1587, "question": "I was on vacation, and in my mind, vacation does not mean setting my hotel room alarm clock for 6 am. But when you're in Aruba and hoping to reserve a beachside palapa , that's exactly what you do. Tourists begin lining up at the crack of dawn to secure these umbrella-like wood structures that are covered with dried and woven palm leaves. They then place towels on chairs and call them theirs for the day, whether they remain there or not. I knew nothing of _ on my first day in Aruba. I saw an empty chair covered with a towel and took it. It was a big mistake. For many visitors, a week bathing in the sun is the only activity they wish to pursue. It sounded good to my girlfriend, Barbara, and me after Boston's awful winter. Six more inches of snow was predicted on the day we left. The sun, th...\n\nQ: What did the author do on his first day there ?", "options": ["He went shopping.", "He swam in the sea.", "He went scuba diving.", "He visited a national park."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 212, "question": "On a small farm in Mexico, there are no schools. A bus is the school! The driver of the bus is the teacher! It is a school bus, but it doesn't take children to school. It just goes round from place to place, and sometimes it comes to this farm. The bus will stay here for three months. The farmers call it a school on wheels . Every time the bus comes, the farmers come running to it, shouting and laughing. They warmly welcome the school bus! When the bus is on the farm, in the morning, the teacher teaches the small children. In the afternoon, the bigger children come to have their lessons because they must work in the morning. At night, the fathers and mothers come to school. They want to learn, too. How the farmers hope that some day they can have a real school on their farm!...\n\nQ: .  . Which one of the following is true?", "options": ["A school bus is a real school for farmers' children.", "The bus school has no teacher at all.", "The bus school has no students.", "The children and their parents on the farm all come to the bus school to learn."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1105, "question": "\"Family\" is of course an _ word. But when British people say that their society is based on family life, they are thinking of \"family\" in its narrow, peculiarly European sense of mother ,father and children living together alone in their own house as an economic and social unit. Thus, every British marriage indicates the beginning of a new and independent family--hence the tremendous importance of marriage in British life. For both the man and the woman, marriage means leaving one's parents and starting one's own life. The man's first duty will then be to his wife, and the wife's to her husband. He will be entirely responsible for her financial support, and she for the running of the new home. Their children will be their common responsibility and theirs alone. Neither the wife's parents n...\n\nQ: Everything is decided in a family   _  .", "options": ["by the couple", "with the help of their parents", "by brothers and sisters", "with the help of aunts and uncles"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1887, "question": "Teen Dating can be fun if you are aware of its pros and cons and are also aware of the ways to protect yourself. There are a couple of suggestions you would like to know before you are out for dating. Do not go out for dating with somebody whom you have seen only a few times and does not know much about him or her. Before leaving on a date, know the exact plans for the evening and make sure a parent or friend knows these plans and what time to expect you home. Let your date know that you are expected to call or tell that person when you get in. Similarly, if you leave a party with someone you do not know well, make sure you tell another person you are leaving and with whom. Ask a friend to call and make sure you arrive home safely. No matter how good the person appears to you, trust your i...\n\nQ: The best title for this passage might be  _  .", "options": ["Be careful with your friends", "Never go out dating", "Safety measures for teen dating", "Dating out is always dangerous"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1172, "question": "Computer power is moving into the \"cloud\"--networks of data centres that use the Internet to supply all kinds of services, from e-mail and social networks to data storage and analysis. The rise of cloud computing is rapid and causing huge changes in the tech industry. The old guard is suffering: this week's $67 billion merger between Dell and EMC, makers of computers and storage devices respectively , was a marriage forced by the rise of the cloud. Disruptive newcomers are blooming: if Amazon's cloud-computing unit were a stand-alone public company, it would probably be worth almost as much as Dell and EMC combined. The gains for customers have been equally dramatic. Compared with older IT systems, cloud computing is often much cheaper. It adds tremendous flexibility: firms that need more ...\n\nQ: The problem of \"lock-in\" can be dangerous because   _  .", "options": ["it should ensure data can easily be moved to another provider", "it can create a network of services connected with devices", "it may make it difficult for customers to recover their data", "it will discourage an argument about stricter rules"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 925, "question": "In ancient Egypt, a shopkeeper discovered that he could attract customers to his shop simply by making changes to its environment. Modern businesses have been following his lead,with more tactics . One tactic involves where to display the goods. Foe example, stores place fruits and vegetables in the first section. They know that customers who buy the healthy food first will feel happy so that they will buy more junk food later in their trip. In department stores, section is generally next to the women's cosmetics section:while the shop assistant is going back to find the right size shoe, bored customers are likely to wander over cosmetics they might want to try later. Besides, businesses seek to appeal to customers' senses. Stores notice that the smell of baked goods encourages shopping, t...\n\nQ: What is the main purpose of the passage?", "options": ["To explain how businesses turn people into their customers.", "To introduces how businesses have grown from the past.", "To report researches on customer behavior.", "To show dishonest business practices."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1226, "question": "A Russian,a Cuban,an American businessman and an American lawyer were on a train traveling across England. The Russian took out a large bottle of vodka, gave each of the men a drink and then threw the rest half bottle of vodka out of the window. \"Why did you do that?\" asked the American businessman. \"There's too much vodka in my country,\" said the Russian,\"And really we have more than we will ever use.\" A little later,the Cuban passed around fine Havana Cigars. Then he threw his out of the window. \"I thought Cuba is not a rich country,\" the businessman said. \"But you threw that very good cigars out of the window!\" \"Cigars,\" the Cuban answered,\"are the cheapest in my country. We have more of them than we know what to do with.\" The American businessman sat quietly for a moment. Then he got u...\n\nQ: The Russian and the Cuban both wanted to   _  .", "options": ["tell the businessman what their countries are rich in", "prove that they were not rich", "ask the two Americans to visit their countries", "make the businessman happy"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 738, "question": "How to protect children Web fans from unsuitable material on-line while encouraging them to use the Internet has long been discussed in the US. For some parents, the Internet can seem like a jungle, filled with danger for their children. But jungles contain wonders as well as danger. With good guides, some education, and a few precautions( ), the wilds of the Internet can be safely navigated. \"Kids have to be on-line. If we tell our kids they can't be allowed to surf the Internet, we're cutting them off from their future,\" said an expert. Most kids have started to use search engines. Many of them are great for finding tons of interesting Internet sites, and they can also locate places where you might not want your kids to go. There are search engines designed just for kids. A certain softw...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true according to the passage?", "options": ["Surfing the Internet is the best way of educating children.", "Using a content screener is most reliable for keeping children from having ways to the Internet.", "Searching engines can help children to select materials fit for them.", "Children's not having chances to go to the Internet may have effect on their progress."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 612, "question": "Educating Girls Is a Real Lifesaver Clare Short knows it. Every developing economist knows it. The World Bank knows it. The education of girls is the surest way to reduce poverty. The reason is simple. All the evidence shows that taking girls out of the fields and homes, and putting them behind desks, raises economic productivity, lowers infant and maternal death rates, reduces birth rates, and improves environmental management. Why, then, are 90 million primary school-age girls around the world not in school? For the same reason that when Charles Dickens was writing David Copperfield 150 years ago girls were absent from the British education system: Men in power mostly prefer _ that way, or are not interested enough in changing the situation to commit energy and money to doing so. The cou...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["The countries where women have great influence and are in power always do worse in girls' education.", "Some organizations such as the World Bank haven't taken the lead in girls' education.", "Some girls in Sudan and Indonesia are bound to live a life without education when they are born.", "Each extra year of school for girls has nothing to do with the birthrate and maternal deaths."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 954, "question": "Three years ago when I was still in the University, I also worked at a restaurant. An old man named Mr. Candido Filio was one of our regular customer at the restaurant. He was one of the most intelligent people I've ever known. Every Sunday the Philippine Star Newspaper had a special page for word puzzles and among his peers , Mr.Filio held the record for solving all the puzzles in less than five minutes. He encouraged me to solve them too, and for months and months, I did my best to beat him but failed. Then one Sunday, I did it! I was able to complete them before anyone else. Everyone cheered for me. He came up to me with a smile and said, \" No one has ever beaten me before. You are the first. I'll have a prize for you tomorrow.\" The next day, he gave me a special Scrabble set. I would h...\n\nQ: After she heard what Mr. Filio said, the author probably felt  _  .", "options": ["amazed", "excited", "touched", "inspired"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 301, "question": "Some years ago on a hot summer day in south Florida a little boy decided to go for a swim in the old swimming hole behind his house.In a hurry to dive into the cool water, he ran out of the back door, leaving behind shoes, socks, and shirt as he went. He flew into the water, not realizing that as he swam toward the middle of the lake, a crocodile was swimming toward him.His mother in the house was looking out of the window and saw the two.In great fear, she ran toward the water, shouting to her son as loudly as she could.Hearing her voice, the little boy became alarmed and made a U-turn to swim to his mother.It was too late.Just as he reached her, the crocodile reached him.From the shore, the mother grabbed her little boy by the arms just as the crocodile snatched his legs.That began an in...\n\nQ: Which of the following will be the best title for the text?", "options": ["Scars of Love", "Women Hold up Half the Sky", "A Terrible Experience", "Don't Judge by Appearances"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 533, "question": "A new study warns that about thirty percent of the world's people may not have enough water by the year 2025. An American organization called Population Action International did the new study. It was more than three hundred and thirty-five million people lack enough water now. The people live in twenty-eight countries. Most of the countries are in Africa or in the Middle East. Population Action International researcher Robert Engelman says by the year 2025, about three thousand million people lack water. At least 18 more countries are expected to have serious water problems. The demand for water keeps increasing. Yet the amount of water on the earth the same. Mr Engelman says the population in countries that lack water is growing in these countries will continue to increase. The report say...\n\nQ: The passage mainly tells us that   _   .", "options": ["water is very important for any people", "PAI did a lot of study about water shortage", "water shortage will be a serious problem facing us in the near future", "controlling the population is the best way to solve the problem of water shortage"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1218, "question": "The word I'm going to introduce to you today is-phubbing. Let's see the definition of this term:phubbing n. the act of snubbing someone in a social setting by looking at your cell phone instead of paying attention As you can probably guess, phubbing is a blend of phone and snubbing. The term was coined by a 23-year-old Melbourne resident Alex Haigh. Obviously, he got fed up with how people are always checking Facebook or Twitter on their phones when they are supposed to be interacting with someone face to face. He wanted to put an end to this social phenomenon, therefore he came up with this catchy term. And it did catch on. The word's earliest media mention dates back to June 2012, and in a little over a year's time, phubbing has already been picked up by almost all the mainstream media o...\n\nQ: The author's attitude towards the act of phubbing can be described as   _  .", "options": ["bearable", "Unacceptable", "reasonable", "understandable"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2704, "question": "Country singer and songwriter Adrienne Young brings together music and agricultural activities.She even included seeds in the album cover of her first CD. Adrienne Young wants people to know that she supports the movement in America to increase local farming.She offers information about agricultural issues on her Web site.And now part of the moneyfrom her third and newest release, \"Room to Grow\",will be donated to help support community gardens. Adrienne Young's family has lived in Florida for seven generations.Her ancestors helped develop the agriculture industry there.The state of Florida is the nation's second largest producer of fruits and vegetables, 'after California. Adrienne Young has said that her interest in nature was shaped by the fact that she did not grow up on a farm.She gre...\n\nQ: The aim to write the passage is to   _   .", "options": ["tell us a singer aims to grow interest in local farming", "show Adrienne Young promotes her third CD album", "praise Adrienne Young for her contributions to agriculture", "call on singers to learn from Adrienne Young"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2309, "question": "Engineers should embrace the arts, Sir John O'Reilly, a fellow of the Institution of Engineering and Technology, argued in a lecture. About 59% of engineering companies in the IET's 2014 survey feared skill shortages could threaten business. \"There is nothing as creative as engineering,\" Sir John told the reporter. He says science, technology, engineering and mathematics - often known as \"Stem\" subjects, are vital for a modern knowledge economy. But there is a massive shortfall in the number of recruits - with a recent study by the Royal Academy of Engineering saying the UK needs to increase by as much as 50% the number of Stem graduates it produces. Delivering this year's Mountbatten Lecture at the Royal Institution, Sir John argued that engineers should recognise the role of the arts in ...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["Lack of creativity makes it difficult for the engineering major to find a satisfactory job.", "The key subjects for engineering majors remain to be maths and the sciences rather than arts.", "University engineering departments should cooperate with art schools to improve the success of products.", "Engineering needs to emphasize its creative side to encourage more young people to choose it as a career."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3300, "question": "Do you feel embarrassed when your mum tries to use slang or when she calls you by your childhood nickname in front of your friends? And how about searching for the nearest exit when your father dances with joy when he finds his favorite CD in the shop? Loving them dearly doesn't prevent you from feeling uncomfortable around them. And parents have to accept that Adam Gopnick, a writer for the New Yorker magazine, said in an article published by the BBC: ''The one thing that is written into the human genome is that exactly at the age of 13, your child... will discover that you are now the most embarrassing, ridiculous and annoying person on the planet.'' A survey by the site YoungPoll.com in 2010 suggested that one in three youngsters is so _ by their parents that they refuse to be seen with...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["The situations on which parents embarrass their children.", "Parents should be careful not to embarrass their children.", "It is normal for teenagers to feel embarrassed with their parents sometimes.", "The generation gap between children and parents is growing."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2050, "question": "It was just three degrees above zero. \"That's cold,\" thought Jane as she got ready to deliver her morning papers. Jane has 50 customers, and on cold mornings when she couldn't ride her bike, it took her more than an hour to make her rounds. As she collected her papers and put them into a big canvas bag, Jane regretted that she hadn't finished her math homework the night before. There was still time. She'd hurry with the papers and finish the math before breakfast. Less than an hour later, Jane was nearly finished. She had only five customers to go. She could then head for home to complete her math while her mom fixed breakfast. As she rounded the corner, she saw a car in the middle of the street. It was Mr. Zimmerman, the elderly man who walked with a walking stick. His car was out of gas....\n\nQ: We know from the reading that  _", "options": ["Jane couldn't find any time to finish her homework", "it took about an hour for Jane to send the papers", "Jane would have her breakfast in the school", "Jane likes to deliver papers on cold mornings"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 277, "question": "Ask a teacher to name the most annoying invention of recent years and they will often mention the mobile phone. Disturbed by the problems they create, many head teachers have ordered that pupils should keep their phones switched off at school. Others have told pupils to leave them at home. However, education researchers at The University of Nottingham believe it is time that phone bans were reassessed, because mobile phones can be a powerful learning aid, they say. Dr Elizabeth Hartnell-Young and her colleagues have reached this conclusion after studying the consequences of allowing pupils in five secondary schools to use either their own mobile phones or the new generation of 'smartphones' in lessons. During the nine-month experiment, 14- to-16-year-old pupils used the phones for a wide r...\n\nQ: When the students first used mobile phones for learning, they  _  .", "options": ["all enjoyed the project very much", "didn't know what they were used for", "didn't fully realize the learning functions of mobile phones", "were surprised that they were allowed to use mobile phones in schools"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2569, "question": "When Steve Jobs was born on Febuary24,1955, in San Francisco , California, his unmarried mother decided to put him for adoption because she wanted a girl. So in the middle of the night, his mother called a lawyer named Paul Jobs and said, \"We have an unexpected baby boy; do you want him?\" But his mother told his future parents to promise that they would send Jobs to college. After Steve Jobs graduated from high school, he went to college but decided to drop out because it was so expensive that he had to sleep on the floor in his friends' rooms. At 20, he and a friend(Steve Wozniak) started a company in a garage on April 1, 1976. Jobs named their company ----Apple in memory of a happy summer he had spent as an orchard in Oregon. After 10 years of hard time and failures, starting from two ki...\n\nQ: It can be inferred that Apple  _  .", "options": ["was founded in Oregon", "developed from a garage", "had a difficult beginning", "had a successful beginning"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 307, "question": "When we say older people shrink, we don't mean they become tiny enough to fit in your pocket! We just mean that it's common for older people to become a little shorter over time. This kind of shrinking can't be reversed, although people can slow or stop this process. But why does shrinking happen at all? Because of gravity (the force that keeps your feet on the ground) , cushions between the bones in the spine , get compressed , which makes a person lose a little height and become shorter. Another reason why some older people shrink is because of osteoporosis . Osteoporosis occurs when bone is broken down and not enough new bone material is made. Over time, bone is said to be lost because it's not being replaced. Bones become smaller and weaker and can easily break if someone with osteopor...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true?", "options": ["For shrinking, people can do nothing about it.", "If someone is injured, he will become shorter.", "Women have smaller and lighter bones than men.", "We aren't as tall at the end of the day as we are at the beginning."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1395, "question": "Lonely Planet Publications is the largest guidebook publisher in the world. With over 650 titles sold in 118 countries, it annually sells six million copies, giving guidance to travelers in locations worldwide. Tony Wheeler and his wife Maureen Wheeler were the founders of Lonely Planet Publications and its first writers. They put together Lonely Planet's first publication- Across Asia on the Cheap. Originally from Australia, the couple had decided to travel from Europe back home to Australia overland-going through the countries of Iran, Afghanistan, Pakistan, India, Nepal, and South-East Asia, to eventually reach Australia. Tourist facilitres were limited in these countries, so if travelers wanted to go there, they had to eat and sleep locally. Many of these travelers were young and adven...\n\nQ: It can be concluded that the Wheelers  _  .", "options": ["have only written two books about cheap traveling", "advocated the idea of traveling more with less money", "eventually made their company from bad to worse", "support other travelers to start a publishing house"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 312, "question": "The computers and the Internet The computer is one of the most important inventions of today. Ever since it was invented, it has changed our lives a lot. People can do a lot of things with the computer. For example, some software can be used too help people finish their work. If one can't finish it at once, the computer can save it so that one can find it quickly the next time. When you talk about computer, you must mention the Internet.. The Internet is a huge worldwide collection of computer networks. A network is a small group of computers working together. You can find information about almost any topic in the world from this network.. For example, you can use the Internet instead of a library to find information about current issues for your homework. You can also find information abo...\n\nQ: What's the author's attitude towards the Internet?", "options": ["If the Internet is used in the right way, it is good for us.", "All the information on the Internet is bad for children.", "We can only use the Internet at home.", "The Internet should always used by adults."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1280, "question": "In 1974, after filling out fifty applications, going through four interviews, and winning one offer, I took what I could get ----- a teaching job at what I considered a distant wild area: western New Jersey. My characteristic optimism was alive only when I reminded myself that I would be doing what I had wanted to do since I was fourteen ------- teaching English. School started, but I felt more and more as if I were in a foreign country. Was this rural area really New Jersey? My students took a week off when hunting season began. I was told they were also frequently absent in late October to help their fathers make hay on the farms. I was a young woman from New York City, who thought that \"Make hay while the sun shines\" just meant to have a good time. But, still, I was teaching English. I ...\n\nQ: The taskmaster's attitude towards the writer after his observation of her class can be described as   _   .", "options": ["cruel but encouraging", "sincere and supportive", "fierce but forgiving", "angry and aggressive"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1198, "question": "You use her as a shoulder to cry on. She texts you back with casual jokes. But she, Xiaoice, is only a virtual chatbot. Xiaoice, Microsoft's latest artificial intelligence robot, was briefly released in 2014, and returnen to WeChat in 2015, where she became a big hit. Millions of young Chinese now exchange messages with her daily, The New York Times reported. On WeChat, Xiaoice is an official account. After following it, users can start text-based conversations with Xiaoice. \"Her incredible learning ability was why people loved to talk with Xiaoice,\" Liu Jinchang, a researcher at High-tech Research and Development Center under the Ministry of Science and Technology, told China Daily. Apart from her ability to identify photos and send emojis m conversations, Xiaoice gains 45 percent of her ...\n\nQ: Which company's chatbot program can act as an academic consultant?", "options": ["Microsoft.", "IBM.", "Apple.", "Amazon."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2301, "question": "Some diaries from Jackie Chan's blog January 4, 2009 Lately I've been busy in Beijing having meetings to discuss my new movie. I also attended John Wu's ceremony of his new movie,Red Cliff,which took two years to complete. I'm good friends with the director John Wu and the main actor Tony Leung. January 5, 2009 Today I went to record a television program for Beijing TV calledVolunteers Across China. This TV program is a large-scale reality show that is based on the idea that \"good people reap good rewards\" and it hopes to encourage people to be more aware and help the \"good people\" who are in difficult situations. January 6, 2009 I'm very pleased to _ that my Jackie Chan automobile website is set up and officially operating! I hope that through this automotive website, I can get in touch w...\n\nQ: What might be the best title for this passage?", "options": ["My new movie.", "My busy life.", "My good friend.", "My favorite song."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 284, "question": "Born in America in 1898, William was an extraordinary boy, gifted with an amazing IQ between 250 and 300. The genius went to a grammar school when he was only 6 years old and graduated just within 7 months. At the age of 11, he became the youngest student of the Harvard University. He graduated with high scores at the age of 16 and entered Harvard Law School at 18. Gifted with an amazing IQ between 220 and 230, Terence Tao makes it to this list of the people with the highest IQ in the world. Born in Adelaide, Australia in 1975, this genius first displayed his incredible intelligence at a mere age of 2, when he managed to solve basic arithmetic questions on his own. At the age of 16, he graduated with both Master's and Bachelor's degrees at the Flinders University. He has been considered as...\n\nQ: About William, which of the following is true?", "options": ["His IQ reached between 220 and 230.", "At the age of 16, he graduated from a grammar school.", "At the age of 6, he graduated with both Master's and Bachelor's degrees.", "At the age of 11, he became the youngest student at the Harvard University."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3195, "question": "Pingviman Hotel Offering an outdoor pool, Pingviman Hotel offers Thai-style rooms in Chiang Mai. Free WiFi is available through-out and a complimentary service takes guests to the Chiang Mai Night Bazaar. All rooms are equipped with a 48-inch flat-screen cable TV and DVD player. Facilities at this hotel include a business center, a fitness center and laundry services. There is also a tour desk and meeting facilities. We speak your language! Hotel Rooms:35 Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel Situated in Chiang Mai's trendiest area, Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel Chiang Mai by Compass Hospitality boasts accommodation in a boutique hotel well-decorated with art works from the renowned local Thai artists. Free WiFi is offered all throughout the property. At Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel, guests will fin...\n\nQ: What's the similarity among the four hotels?", "options": ["They all have an outdoor pool.", "They all equip the hotel rooms with cable TVs.", "They all have a center for fitness.", "They all provide free WiFi service."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 394, "question": "There's a man in the habit of hitting me on the head with an umbrella.At first I couldn't stand it;now I'm used to it. I don't know his name.I know he's average in appearance,wears a gray suit.and has a common face one hot morning,when 1 was sitting off a tree-shaded bench in Palermo Park,reading the paper,suddenly I felt something touch my head.It was the very same man who now,as I'm writing.keeps striking me with an umbrella. On that occasion I turned around filled with anger.He just kept on hitting me.I asked him if he was crazy.He didn't even seem to hear me.Thell I threatened to call a policeman.Calmly.cool as a cucumber,he stuck with his task.After a few moments of hesitation,and seeing that he was not about to change his attitude,I stood up and hit him on the nose.The man fell down....\n\nQ: The author felt sorry for the man because_.", "options": ["the man formed a bad habit of beating others", "he hit I the marl so hard that his nose bled", "the man couldn't catch up with him", "there was a fly on the man's head"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1031, "question": "Some kinds of mental skills naturally decrease as people get older. Yet research seems to show that some training can improve such skills. A recently published study also appears to demonstrate that the good effects of training can last for many years after that training has ended. Researchers at Johns Hopkins University in Maryland wanted to learn how long memory and thinking skills would last in older people who trained to keep them. The people were part of the ten-year research project. They were taught methods meant to improve their memory, thinking and ability to perform everyday tasks. More than 2,800 volunteered for the study called ACTIVE - short for Advanced (Cognitive) Training for Independent and Vital Elderly. Most studied when they were more than 70 years old. The volunteers t...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of the fourth paragragh?", "options": ["What was the meaning of the research?", "How was the research conducted?", "Why was the mental training effective?", "How long did the research last?"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3127, "question": "In the last 500 years nothing about people--not their clothes, ideas, or languages has changed as much as what they eat. Chocolate drink was first made from the seeds of the cacao tree by South American Indians. The Spanish introduced it to the rest of the world during the 1500s. And although it was very expensive, it quickly became popular, In London, shops where chocolate drinks were served became important places. Some still exist today. The potato is also from the New World. Around 1600, the Spanish brought it from Peru to Europe, where it soon was widely grown. Ireland became so dependent on it that thousands of Irish people starved when the crop failed during the years of 1845--1846, and thousands more were forced to go to live in America. There are many other foods that have travele...\n\nQ: According to the passage, who first made chocolate drink from the seeds of the cacao tree?", "options": ["People in Peru", "People in Brazil.", "South American Indians.", "People in Ethiopia."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1503, "question": "Columbus made four voyages to the west between 1492 and 1504 in his vain search for a sea route to Asia. The mystery of why he failed to find it haunted him and filled him with sadness. Wherever he went to Cuba, Puerto Rico, Jamaica, South America, Panama, down the coast of Central America--it was always the same story. Instead of golden palaces, there were grass huts and palm-leaf tents. Instead of silk-robed merchant princes, he found \"Indians\" who did not have so much as a shirt on their backs. When Columbus explored the West Indies in 1493,he heard tales of a fierce Indian tribe who literally devoured its defeated enemies after a battle. These people were called by many names in the area, including Calina, Canima, Carib, and Caniba. Columbus recorded the name of the American natives as...\n\nQ: In the course of his four voyages, Columbus succeeded in   _  .", "options": ["finding China and the Spice Islands", "trading with many merchants", "visiting several parts of Central and South America", "sailing to Asia"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 645, "question": "Earthquakes are something that people fear. There are some places that have few or no earthquakes. Most places in the world, however, have them regularly . Countries that have a lot of earthquakes are usually quite mountainous. The most talked about earthquake in the United States was in San Francisco in 1906. Over 700 people died in it. The strongest one in North America was in 1964. It happened in Alaska. Strong earthquakes are not always the ones that kill the most people. In 1755, one of the strongest earthquakes ever recorded was felt in Portugal. Around 2,000 people died. In 1923, a very strong earthquake hit Tokyo, the Yokohama area of Japan. A hundred and forty thousand people died. Most of them died in fires which followed the earthquake. One of the worst earthquakes ever was in C...\n\nQ: When and where was the worst earthquake ever recorded?", "options": ["1964; Alaska.", "1923; Japan.", "1976; China.", "1556; China."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2216, "question": "Picking up objects plays an important role in people's life. El-E is a robot that is designed to get everyday objects for people with disabilities. About 1.5 meters tall, with a single robotic arm that can pick up objects at different heights, El-E is equipped to discover what its owner wants and then go and fetch it. The user can point a location to the robot using a \"point-and-click\" way of interaction, which provides a direct way to tell the robot which object to handle or where to go. The robot can adapt the position of its arm in order to grasp the object. After successful early trials, some scientists expanded El-E's functions and tried to combine voice commands with the laser in order to do more complicated tasks, like opening doors. The robot recognizes words such as \"pull\" or \"pus...\n\nQ: From the text, we can learn that  _  .", "options": ["robots are getting more and more popular", "robots are quicker than human beings", "more and more people begin to develop robots for the disabled", "correcting mistakes can help the robot work more successfully"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3243, "question": "Dr. Paul Kelly, head of Monkeseaton Community High School in North Tyneside, said it would mean the end of sleeping in lessons before lunch, after experiments showed teenagers could have different body clocks from adults and younger children. Russell Foster, an Oxford professor of neuroscience , tested the memory of 200 Monkseaton pupils at 9 am and 2 pm using pairs of words, and discovered a 9% improvement in the afternoon. Students correctly identified 51% of word pairs in the latest session, compared with 42% in the morning. Tayler McCullough, 15, one of the test subjects, said the majority of students would welcome the extra hours in bed, \"I'm extremely hard to get up in the morning. One or two people like to get to school early, but most of us would be up for going in later. I'm sure ...\n\nQ: According to Russell Foster's research,   _  .", "options": ["the students tested had very good memories", "the students tested did better jobs in the afternoon", "42% of the students tested could do very good jobs", "51% of the students tested could master 9% of words"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3060, "question": "China, known as the \"kingdom of bicycle\", will see a quick growth in electric bicycle production in the next five years thanks to the country's efforts to save energy and improve the environment. The output of electric bikes is expected to maintain an annual growth rate of at least 80 percent in the coming five years. China will _ 30 million electricity-driven bikes in 2020, compared to 9 million bikes last year, according to a report from the Development Research Center under the State Council and other ministries such as the National Development and Reform Commission. The central government wants to reduce the amount of energy consumption by as much as 20 percent within the next five years. That would be achieved through the introduction of new sources of energy and encouraging people to...\n\nQ: Why will there be a quick growth in electric bicycle production in the next five years in China?", "options": ["Because electric bicycles can save the consumer more money.", "Because the central government encourages people to save energy.", "Because most people in China can't afford cars.", "Because the Chinese government limits the development of bicycle production."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2841, "question": "My challenge for you is this: to read a book for 15 minutes every single day for a month. Let me explain a bit, by telling you where the challenge came from. I have many things in common with my dad, like music taste and sense of humor, but sadly reading isn't one of them. I can happily spend a whole day with a book, but my dad can't read a book for longer than about 5 minutes. He reads emails, websites and papers for work, but not books. He's busy so I think sitting down to read for just 15 minutes a day is a good way to relax and to introduce him to reading. My dad is by no means the only person who avoids books. I know lots of people would rather relax on their computers or in front of the TV. Everyone is different and has their own interests, but I think there're lots of benefits to re...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be the best title for the text?", "options": ["Tips for Reading English Books", "15-Minute Reading Challenge", "Having a Coffee While You Read", "Ways to Improve Reading Skills"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1568, "question": "Sports, drama, and a variety of organizations keep students busy during high school. Where do they find the money to do these things? Not everyone gets it from Mommy and Daddy. Most have to pay for these activities. Some adults question if high school students should have jobs. Some people worry that teens with after-school jobs will struggle to find time for homework. Actually, the responsibility of having a job helps teens prioritize their time. Many jobs take only a couple of hour shifts on weeknights. According to a survey, 86 percent of high school students have an after-school, weekend or summer job and students who work between 10 and 20 hours per week during the school year have statistically higher grades-point averages than those who do not work at all. Those who work in high sch...\n\nQ: The author's attitude towards teens having after-school jobs is  _  .", "options": ["cautious", "unconcerned", "supportive", "negative"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3118, "question": "Chocolate soap is supposed to be good for the skin. But it's not so good for the tongue. Unfortunately for the US soldiers of World War II, the chocolate bars the army gave them tasted like they were intended for use in the bath. In the army's defense, it wasn't trying to win any cooking awards. In fact, it specifically ordered that its chocolate bars not be too delicious, so soldiers wouldn't eat them too quickly. These bars were created for survival, not taste. \"They were awful,\" John Otto, a former army captain in World War II said, \"They were big, thick things, and they weren't any good. I tried them, but I had to be awfully hungry after I tried them once.\" As unappealing as the chocolate bars were to some, others like them. Samuel Hinkle, the chemist who created the chocolate bars, po...\n\nQ: Why does the author mention the German kids' story?", "options": ["To tell how friendly the American soldiers were.", "To show how much they were eager for chocolate.", "To prove German kids could be very polite.", "To describe the hunger in Germany during the war."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2451, "question": "Today, Mount Qomolangma's peak is not a lonely place any more. More than 3,500 people have successfully climbed the 8,844m mountain, and more than a tenth of that number reached the peak just over the past year. As more and more people try to test themselves against Qomolangma, many a time the mount can be very crowded. Climbers have complained about waiting for hours in the bottlenecks on the way to the peak. If bad weather strikes, climbers can and do die. But the dangerous crowds aren't the only problem on Qomolangma. All those climbers need to bring a lot of _ --much of them ends up being left on the mountain, sometimes even the peak itself. Mount Qomolangma is becoming the world's tallest rubbish dump. Here's mountaineer Mark Jenkins writing in National Geographic about the state of Q...\n\nQ: What can be the best title for the text?", "options": ["Test Yourself Against Qomolangma", "Qomolangma has Become a Huge Mess", "Eco Everest Expedition Proves Successful", "How to Climb Qomolangma"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1320, "question": "Recently educators have been questioning \"prep school\" (=preparatory school) where barely literate high school athletes get their transcripts by taking courses occasionally and sometimes by taking no courses at all. The athletes then go on to famous sports universities, where they exhaust their playing years before landing back on the streets without job opportunity or college degrees. The prep school scheme was meant to avoid academic qualification rules for college athletes made years ago by the National Collegiate Athletic Association. The N.C.A.A., which was slow to recognize the seriousness of the problem, has finally adopted policies to root it out. But those policies will not do the job unless everyone is involved, including prep schools and college athletics departments that still ...\n\nQ: Having recognized the seriousness of the prep school scheme, the N.C.A.A. has taken all the measures EXCEPT  _  .              .", "options": ["investigating and checking some prep school program", "shutting down some unqualified prep school", "listing compulsory courses and the number of course needed to be taken in high school", "checking some problematic transcripts"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2939, "question": "Crazy is our new normal. With two teenage boys and three little boys, our family is restless--to the baseball field, track field and piano lessons. Even though we've limited each boy's activities and try our best to defend our family time, it seems that we're in a constant state of flight. \"Embrace it. Roll with it,\" my husband, Lonny, says, \"It's going to be like this for a while.\" He is right. It's likely that life will continue to go forward before it slows down. But I remembered the still, quiet days that our family used to enjoy. I missed long walks through the park when we held the boys' little hands. I longed for lazy Saturday afternoons under the tree in our backyard. I wanted to slip back a few years, when busyness was the exception and not the rule. One night, after a particularl...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements might the author agree to?", "options": ["Life is nothing but bitterness, busyness and horror.", "Happiness is everywhere, but we have to discover it.", "Parents should earn much money for their kids' better life.", "Life in the countryside is charming, wonderful, and sweet."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2274, "question": "According to a famous optical expert, Alexander, who recently visited Shanghai, the developed countries in Europe and America have made rules that children must wear resinous glasses instead of the traditional glasses made of glass. This is because the glass glasses are more likely to do harm to children's eyesight. Alexander pointed out: wearing the right glasses as soon as possible is still the best way to cure and put right children's eyesight problems. In America and Japan the resinous glasses have taken up 80 percent of the glasses market. And some European countries and America have made it a law that children, teenagers and drivers must wear resinous glasses. Now, about 10 million children in China have different eyesight problems and they need timely treatment. But still, too many ...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from this news text that   _  .", "options": ["resinous glasses are not on sale in China yet", "resinous glasses are not acceptable in China", "glass glasses have disappeared on western market because there is a law against them", "glass glasses are the first choice in China not only because of their price"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3007, "question": "People bury treasure to stop other people from taking it. They choose a quiet place, dig a deep hole and bury the treasure in it. Then they make a map of where the treasure is or write down other clues that will help them or someone else to find it again. In Britain a few years ago, a writer wrote about some treasure that he had buried. He put clues in the story to help readers find it. Thousands of people hunted for the treasure. They dug holes all over Britain, hoping to find it. One of the most popular adventure stories ever written is Robert Louis Stephenson's \"Treasured Island\", an exciting story about a young boy, Jim Hawkins, who is captured by pirates and later finds some buried treasure. Then there is the true story about a man who had to travel overseas for a year. He did not tru...\n\nQ: The man who buried his money in a park    _    .", "options": ["thought his money was safer there than in a bank.", "travelled on the sea for a year.", "got his life savings back again.", "stayed away longer than he expected."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3135, "question": "For some reason, it takes constant reminders that weprimates need nurturing. In a recent study of 46 babychimpanzee orphans, Kim Bard of the University of Portsmouth in England and her colleagues demonstrated that primate babies that have tight relationships with mother figures do much better oncognitive tests than babies who receive only food, shelter, and friendship with peers. But this is not breaking mews. In fact, it's old news. In the 1950s, Harry Harlow conducted a series of experiments with baby monkeys that showed, without doubt, that lack of love and comfort makes for a crazy monkey. Harlow constructed a cage that included a wire monkey \"mother\" topped with a plastic face. In this wire he fixed Mom with a milk bottle. The cage also held another wire mother covered with terry clot...\n\nQ: Why was Harlow's monkey work important?", "options": ["Because the \"no touch, no comfort\" policy toward children was quite right.", "Because parents were advised not to respond to babies' crying.", "Because Harlow's work changed people's former belief in child care.", "Because mothers were not allowed to have their newborns next to them in the hospital."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1589, "question": "In 1969 I was a young girl working in Toronto. I was from a small town in Ontario and had just moved to the big city about three months earlier. It was one week before Christmas and I was going home on the last streetcar of the evening. I remember looking at my paycheque and asking myself how it was going to endure. At that time in my life I hardly had enough money to exist on. Bread for supper and oatmeal for breakfast was the only way I kept hunger at bay. I got off the streetcar and started walking up the street, when I suddenly noticed a man was running after me. I stopped, turned around, seeing that he was black. I _ , \"What do you want?\" The man answered in a soft voice, \"I am returning your wallet. You left it on the streetcar seat.\" Because of that man's thoughtfulness, I was allow...\n\nQ: What is the writer trying to tell her readers?", "options": ["Never judge people by their appearance.", "She had been struggling to her success.", "She had changed a lot since that night.", "Being kind to strangers will pay back."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1911, "question": "When we look at the sky and see a bright light moving quickly across it or coming towards the earth, we talk about seeing a \"shooting star\" or a \"falling star\". These moving lights are not, in fact, stars at all. They are small pieces of matter from outer space, which burn up as they enter the Earth's atmosphere. The correct name of them is meteoroids. Any pieces that make it to the Earth's surface without completely burning up are known as meteorites. A meteor is actually the name given to the light we see when a meteoroid is burning up. When a meteorite hits the Earth at speeds between 11 and 72 kilometers a second, it can do amazing damage. A very large meteorite could knock the earth out of its orbit. If this happened, all life on Earth would probably become extinct . The path we follo...\n\nQ: The story is about   _  .", "options": ["floods caused by meteors", "matter from outer space", "life on Earth millions of years ago", "meteorites that have damaged the moon"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 495, "question": "Warm weather brought by El Nino has had mixed effects on animals in usually snowy places in North America, including New England, according to an Associated Press article. Some animals seem to benefit from having a chance to gather more food before winter, and from expending less energy in daily survival mode. Others, like snowshoe hares, are put at center stage in predators' view when they lack snow for disguising their white fur -- not a good thing for them, of course. Black bears, on the other hand, have been keeping busy gathering nuts and apples, when they would normally have settled into their winter homes by now. Vermont and Massachusetts officials have asked residents to wait till snow falls to take out their bird feeders for the sake of safety, the article said. \"We suggest waitin...\n\nQ: What do the bear biologist's words imply?", "options": ["A heavy snow is on the way.", "Bears are common nowadays.", "Bears live mainly on birds in winter.", "Warm weather benefits birds in winter."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 139, "question": "Dear Earthmen , I have enjoyed my stay on your interesting unusual planet. I think I understand the life on earth now and I would like to give you my impressions. First of all you live in boxes. Every morning you leave your big boxes and get into smaller boxes on wheels. All these small boxes race around and around, and finally stop to rest. You then leave these boxes on wheels and go to very large tall boxes. After testing all days you get back in your little boxes and return to your big boxes. There you sit and stare at tiny glowing boxes with moving pictures on the front. Only one thing puzzles me. One day I went to a football game. A bunch of angry boys fought over a little round ball. Everyone yelled for them to stop but they kept on fighting. They were angry, I suppose, about being c...\n\nQ: The best title of this passage is  _  .", "options": ["The Man from the Mars", "Something about Boxes", "A Letter from the Mars", "A Football Game"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2867, "question": "Be Healthy! Be Slim! Be Beautiful! Discover the secret for a Healthy, Slim, Beautiful You! Discover how to be Healthy, Slim and Beautiful! I love this healthy diet program because it helps you lose weight, lose inches, feel healthy and look beautiful. This healthy diet is an 8-week program which is unlike other diet regimes because it focuses on proper nutritional first and weight loss second. Your body must have proper levels of minerals, vitamins, and protein in order to work well. It provides a simply lifestyle change to give you more energy and improve your health most greatly. It offers control over stomach and continuing hunger with a calorie dense diet allowing 1,700 to 2,000 calories a day. If a person has a weight problem their body probably is not working at proper levels of basi...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT TRUE ?", "options": ["This program makes a change in your lifestyle.", "This program can stop you from feeling hungry all the time.", "This program allows you 1700 to 2000 calories for each meal.", "The program can offer control over your stomach."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 703, "question": "\"The days when the management in Western companies presented gold watches to long-serving employees to thank them for loyal service is now just a memory.\" says the Educational and Training Support Agency. This new development in the shape and movement of the workforce throughout Western businesses is partly a result of the way that layers of middle management are being removed, leaving more workers responsible for their own development. \"Having workers take responsibility for their own development might be dramatic, but it is now the rule,\" says the Educational and Training Support Agency. \"Today, not only are workers more mobile, they have to run to keep up with changes.\" says the Government-founded agency.\"It is no longer enough for a worker to gain a set of skills.Workers need the abili...\n\nQ: The passage seems to suggest that the present situation in society requires that workers should", "options": ["show more loyalty to their companies", "try to develop their skills to fit in with changes", "go to college to have their skills up to date", "be quick in changing their careers if there is the possibility"], "answer": 1}]